Once again, we are pleased to present with the cooperation of Yukari Resort Gehlot Saijo Raku.
It has begun. It's a hachimakegakuen.
This time, too, it's a school trip.
This is Nao.
I'm Sataka.
So, here we are this time!
Teyaki and Chinomi rice crackers
This is Senjyudo.
It's a rice cracker.
Tochinomi, tochinomi, tochinoki
This? This?
Look, it's a tree, isn't it?
Tochinoki (Japanese horse chestnut)
Japanese horse chestnut (Aesculus hippocastanum)
What's it called?
It's another name?
Is this what the body grows on?
What is this?
Tuchinomi.
It looks like an acorn. Round.
Like chestnuts or acorns.
It does look like a chestnut.
Inside of a chestnut.
It's hard.
It says something.
It is a tochinomi from the Gero market.
In the Hitachi area, where crops are scarce in winter,
Tochinomi was a valuable relief food.
Even today, there is still a custom in some areas to eat Tochisen at New Year's,
Tochisen is still eaten in some areas.
It is said to be 30 times more potent than polyphenolaic wine.
Isn't that amazing?
It is also rich in tannin, which is effective against rough skin.
So it's full of nutrients?
That's so good!
That's amazing.
I think I'm going to get a little bit of a "soboshin.
How do you eat it?
Bare fangs.
It's that hard.
It's hard.
Can I come in?
There are many desserts on the menu.
The aroma here is amazing.
Then I'd like to go in.
Kinkon, kankon.
Excuse me for disturbing you.
Sorry to bother you.
It smells so good.
This is Tochimomi senbei.
Amazing. There are so many sweets.
Is there such a thing as warm rice crackers?
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Just baked.
Are they rice crackers?
Yes, they are.
Are these rice crackers your signature product?
Also, there is a rice cracker called "Tochimomi Senbei," which has a shelf life of 30 seconds.
Thirty seconds?
What do you mean?
Freshly baked rice crackers are soft.
After about 30 seconds, they become hard and crispy.
Do you mean that you eat them when they are soft?
I mean before it gets hard.
I want to try it.
I'd like to try that.
Because you can only eat it here, right?
That's right.
Is this real?
This is the real thing.
I didn't know they had such a big one.
This one is the real thing.
This is the real one.
You want me to sleep with this in my mouth?
This one, you know, I take it from the collar, turn it to open well, and put it inside the rice cracker.
I see.
So, before you eat the Tochimomi rice cracker, which has an expiration date of 30 seconds,
I would like to try the hard rice cracker in normal mode first. It looks delicious.
It's so crispy, you can tell by its appearance. Yes, this is definitely hard.
Then, let's eat it.
Oh, so this is how it feels. It's light. Bon appétit.
Nice sound.
Bon appétit.
Crispy.
It's very gentle sweetness.
It tastes very easy to eat. Delicious.
Delicious.
Sweet.
Okay, I'll have two pieces, please.
Yes, 2 pieces.
30 seconds.
I'm so excited.
Bon appétit.
Wow! It's here!
Is it done?
Here you go.
30 seconds!30 seconds!
Bon appétit.
It's soft.
Look how it bends.
It's hot!
Bon appétit.
Hot, hot, hot.
It's totally different!
Tastes different.
Delicious!
I can't believe how different it feels when the texture changes.
Oh, it's done!
It's getting hard.
You can't prove it!
But earlier, you said it was crispy when you chewed it.
You don't say that anymore.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's soft.
It's getting a little harder.
It's getting crispy.
Oh! It's already crispy!
Yeah, I could really prove it in 30 seconds.
But you can enjoy it from here, too.
Yum, yum.
Yum! Yum!
Don't you want to try something else on the menu?
Even if I want to try Mont Blanc.
Chiffon cake.
We have all kinds of cakes.
Let's eat.
May I? Yes!
Yay!
Let's think.
Oh!
Yes!
Finish up, here.
Chiffon cake with glutinous rice cake and ice cream on top.
Ice cream?
Mont Blanc cream with sticky rice cake.
Yes!
Mochinomi all the way!
Yes, please! I'm so excited!
I may have never seen it before. We can make Mont Blanc!
Oh, hey, look at this!
I want to take a picture.
Wow! It's Aubrun! Wow! Wow! That's a lot! Hey!
Looks delicious!
Wow! Wow! It's full of stuff! Looks delicious!
And there it is,
Powder!
Wow!
Crunchy!
It sure changes the texture!
Thank you!
Looks delicious!
Wow! Such a big one!
Amazing!
Let's have some!
Delicious!
This...this...what do you call it?
Are there fruits of the land in these whirlpools and eddies?
Yes! They're all from the land!
Aren't they amazing?
They're full of polyphenols!
Yes! 30 times more than wine!
Yes! Bon appétit!
Den!
Whoo!
How's it going? How's it going? Well?
Yoo-hoo! This powder is so good!
Bon appétit!
It changes the texture, doesn't it?
Yum! Yum! Yes! Yes!
It's delicious.
It's rice cracker powder.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Oh, no, not at all!
Yeah.
I just got the ice cream.
Ice cream is bad.
Ice cream bad?
Yeah! I want some!
I want ice cream.
It's so sweet.
Mmm!
Yummy.
It's too good!
I've never had such a delicious Mont Blanc.
Right?
The sweetness is amazing!
It's not too sweet.
Yes, it's sweet and refreshing.
It's very natural.
Yes, that's right.
That's right.
This is so good!
Wait, wait, wait.Wait, wait, wait.
I like it best.
Me too.
My favorite in the world of sweets.
I also like Mont Blanc the best
chew
I like this cake from now on
It's delicious
The potential of the land fruit is amazing
I agree.
I don't know...
The potential for the future looks amazing.
Yeah.
It's so nutritious.
Mont Blanc is the only way to go.
Mont Blanc is the ultimate?
And the possibilities are endless.
Oh no! The fruit of the land!
Mont Blanc is what you think of chestnuts!
Chestnuts are scared.
Yeah...
Oh, that seat there...
They're going to take our place.
The fruits of the land...
They're probably not as famous as chestnuts.
I think they'll come.
Everyone should try one.
It's too good!
Oh, man.
It's so good!
I can't stop.
Yeah, it's really good!
Oh, it's so good! It's so good!
We had rice crackers with an expiration date of 30 seconds, rice crackers in normal mode, and Mont Blanc!
I had the normal mode rice crackers and the Mont Blanc!
They were all great, but I felt that even though they all had rice crackers in them...
I agree, the powder on top of the Mont Blanc is like rice cracker powder, so...
I knew those rice crackers were great!
The crackers make the Mont Blanc taste so much better.
It changes the texture so much.
I'm amazed at the taste of the land.
I wish I'd known about them earlier.
I'm definitely going to stop by when I'm in Gero! It was so delicious!
And the projection!
Okay, let's get this out of here.
Here we go!
I think it looks good.
It's delicious. I mean, it's delicious.
I mean, it's delicious. It looks good and it's delicious.
It was delicious, wasn't it?
We ate a lot of delicious food.
I was very happy!
Thank you very much for your help last week.
Well, I'm off to the next place!
It's time for Hatsuchi News!
We, Team Hatsuchi, are now on a 3 free live tour!
We are touring in various places!
We'll be performing live and having special events.
Please come and see us!
And, you know what?
On June 3, Yuzuki will be holding a festival called Yuzuki's Hair Fest.
Yuzuki will be holding a festival on June 3.
The biggest one.
That's right.
That's great.
This is the third time.
This time it will be held at the new Zepp Shinjuku.
This will be our first time to visit Zepp Shinjuku!
Yuzuki will shine very brightly!
Please come and join us!
We look forward to seeing you there!
And what's more...
This summer, isn't it?
July 22nd, right?
We will be holding an Orca Festival at Nagoya Castle!
Yay, Killer Whale!
It's our one-man show for the summer.
Last year, we came back after a long absence.
In the open air and at Nagoya Castle!
The place where we started.
Yes, Nagoya Castle is where we made our debut on the street.
So I'm really looking forward to seeing Orca-sama at the place of my memories.
I'm really looking forward to it!
Just thinking about it makes me emo.
I know, it's so bad, isn't it?
And I'm feeling it too.
After all, it's really hot in Nagoya in the summer.
I want to do a live show that won't let the heat get the better of me.
I'd like to do a live show that won't let the heat get the better of me.
Please come to Nagoya Castle on July 22nd!
We're looking forward to seeing you there!
That's all for now!